<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Meet @ OsloMet</string>


    <!-- Preference strings are to be left empty in this file -->
    <string name="preference_AuthKey"></string>
    <string name="preference_username"></string>
    <string name="preference_validate">false</string>
    <string name="preference_setPassword">false</string>
    <string name="preference_matchPreference">0</string>
    <string name="preference_idUser"></string>


    <string name="title_activity_match">ActivityMatch</string>


    <string name="gender0">Male</string>
    <string name="gender1">Female</string>
    <string name="gender2">Other</string>
    <string name="genderSelect">Please select your gender</string>

    <!-- Array strings -->
    <string-array name="genders">
        <item>@string/genderSelect</item>
        <item>@string/gender0</item>
        <item>@string/gender1</item>
        <item>@string/gender2</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="position0">Bachelor student</string>
    <string name="position1">Master/PhD student</string>
    <string name="position2">Academic staff</string>
    <string name="position3">Administrative staff</string>
    <string name="position4">Other</string>

    <string-array name="positions">
        <item>@string/position0</item>
        <item>@string/position1</item>
        <item>@string/position2</item>
        <item>@string/position3</item>
        <item>@string/position4</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="campus1">Pilestredet</string>
    <string name="campus2">Kjeller</string>
    <string name="campus3">Sandvika</string>

    <string-array name="campuses">
        <item>@string/campus1</item>
        <item>@string/campus2</item>
        <item>@string/campus3</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="languages_array">
        <item>English</item>
        <item>Japanese</item>
        <item>French</item>
        <item>Spanish</item>
        <item>Norwegian</item>
        <item>Danish</item>
        <item>Dutch</item>
        <item>Swedish</item>
        <item>German</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="countryCode_array">
        <item>GB</item>
        <item>JP</item>
        <item>FR</item>
        <item>ES</item>
        <item>NO</item>
        <item>DK</item>
        <item>NL</item>
        <item>SE</item>
        <item>DE</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="legalNote">"By using this application or related software you agree that you have read and accept the &lt;a href=https://meet.vlab.cs.hioa.no/legal/tou.html>terms of use&lt;/a> and that you are familiar with the &lt;a href=https://meet.vlab.cs.hioa.no/legal/privacyPolicy.html>privacy policy&lt;/a>"</string>

    <string name="campusDefault">Please select your camps</string>

    <string name="title_activity_chat">ActivityChat</string>

    <string name="recommended_lang0">Speaks</string>
    <string name="recommended_lang1">Needs help with</string>

    <string name="fragment_tandem_requestsTitle">People wanting to chat</string>
    <string name="fragment_tandem_tandemTitle">Messages</string>

    <string name="fragment_tandem_lastMessage">You: Hallaaa &#8226; 12:01</string>
    <string name="fragment_tandem_lastMessage_placeholder">Click here to see more…</string>


    <string name="text_login">Sign in</string>
    <string name="text_register">Register</string>
    <string name="text_usernameTitle">Student number or employee username</string>
    <string name="text_goback">Go back</string>
    <string name="text_confirm">Confirm</string>
    <string name="text_password">Password</string>
    <string name="text_first_name">First name</string>
    <string name="text_last_name">Last name</string>

    <string name="text_confirm_password">Confirm Password</string>

    <string name="title_activity_terms">Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="terms_text">
       "The application will give information such as name, age, language interest and qualifications"
        "at OsloMet.The hobbies of user are also shown which helps to find a correct match."
        "All the students and staff at OsloMet who are registered in the app can use the app and"
        "communicate with their matches. A matching algorithm is used to find the correct match "
        "based on their language interest and hobbies. \n\n"
        "The institution carries no responsibilities for misuse of this application and the "
        "communication and information exchanged between the user and their match. How much "
        "information is shared must be controlled by the user themselves and focus should be made"
        "in learning and exchanging knowledge about language they want to learn."

    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_privacy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="privacy_text">
        "Privacy Policy\n\n"
        "1) Brief presentation of the Meet@OsloMet app\n\n"

        "The application will give information such as name, age, language interest and qualifications"
        "at OsloMet.The hobbies of user are also shown which helps to find a correct match."
        "All the students and staff at OsloMet who are registered in the app can use the app and"
        "communicate with their matches.\n\n"

        "2) About this privacy policy\n\n"

        "This privacy policy describes how Your University/University College manages your personal"
        "data in the Meet@OsloMet app. The purpose of this privacy policy is to inform you of the "
        "types of personal data processed, how it is processed, who is responsible for the processing,"
        "your rights and whom to contact.\n\n"


        "3)What is personal data?\n\n"

        "The term personal data includes any data, information and assessment that can be linked to "
        "you as an individual, cf. GDPR Article 4 no. 1. The determining factor in whether data is "
        "considered personal information, is whether it is fit to identify a specific person."
        "In some cases, data which, on its own, cannot be linked to an individual person, may "
        "constitute personal data if it is used in combination with other data.\n\n"



        "4)The purpose of the processing of personal data in the Meet@OsloMet app.\n\n"
        "Purpose\n"
        "The purpose of processing personal data in the Meet@OsloMet app is to match the language"
        "interests and hobbies with other registered users of the app and provide suitable partners"
        "to help learn a new language\n\n"

        "Legal basis\n"

        "For Universities/University Colleges who has chosen institutional use:\n"

        "The legal basis for the processing of personal data in the Meet@OsloMet app is GDPR Article 6"
        "no, 1 litra c, cf. no. 3 litra b, and provisions in the Act Relating to Universities and "
        "University Colleges § 4-15.\n\n"

        "For Universities/University Colleges who has chosen personal use:\n"
        "Statutory authority for the processing of personal data in the Meet@OsloMet app is based on"
        "consent. Students are asked to give consent when logging on to the app.\n\n"

        "5) Which kinds of personal data are processed in the Meet@OsloMet app, and how long to we"
        "store your personal data?\n"
        "The Meet@OsloMet app shows your name and qualifications, and whether you are staff or "
        "student of OsloMet. The personal data presented in the app is retrieved from the study"
        "administration system Common Student System (FS), as well as FEIDE (Joint Electronic Identity),"
        "which is the Ministry of Education and Research’s preferred solution for secure identification"
        "in the education sector. The data is stored locally on your device and you may delete them"
        "whenever you want.\n"

        "Downloading the app and logging on is entirely voluntary, and you control to whom you invite"
        "in the app. Using the app is voluntary. If you choose not to use the app you may, at most"
        "universities and university colleges, there are other language learning spaces.\n\n"

        "6) Automatic processing\n"
        "Your personal data will not be made subject to automated processing or profiling.\n\n"

        "7) Disclosure of your personal data to third parties\n"
        "Disclosure or export of data is defined as any transfer of data save for use in the "
        "controller’s own systems/processing or to the data subject itself or any other party "
        "receiving data on the data subject’s behalf.\n"

        "Your personal data will not be disclosed to countries outside of the EU/EEA, or to any "
        "international organizations.\n\n"

        "Your personal data may be disclosed to the following parties/agencies:\n"

        "UNINETT AS\n"
        "When you log in to the Meet@OsloMet app, you use the log-in services FEIDE and Dataporten."
        "FEIDE and Dataporten are developed and provided by UNINETT AS. UNINETT AS staff may access"
        "your FEIDE user name and IP address, provided they need such access in order to perform "
        "their duties. They need this access in order to provide user support and, if relevant, "
        "correct errors as part of their duties. Your personal data will be erased from FEIDE after"
        "six months.\n\n"

        "8) Personal data safety\n"
        "To protect your personal data in the Meet@OsloMet app, various security measures have been"
        "implemented; all transfers to the app are encrypted. In addition, Unit regularly perform"
        "risk and vulnerability analyses and testing of the security in the Meet@OsloMet app.\n\n"

        "9) Your rights\n"
        "Right to information and access\n"
        "You have the right to information about how your University/University College processes "
        "your personal data. The purpose of this privacy policy is to provide you with any and all"
        "information you have the right to get.\n"
        "You also have the right to view/access any and all personal data registered about you at"
        "your University/University College. You also have the right to request a copy of the "
        "personal data registered about you if you so wish.\n\n"

        "Right to correction\n"
        "You have the right to have corrected any and all incorrect personal data about you. You"
        "also have the right to supplement any and all incomplete data registered about you. Please"
        "contact us if you believe we have registered incorrect or incomplete personal data about"
        "you. It is important that you justify and, if relevant, document why you believe the "
        "personal data registered is incorrect or incomplete.\n\n"

        "Right to limit processing\n"
        "In certain circumstances, you have the right to demand limited processing of your personal"
        "data. Limiting the processing of personal data means that your personal data will still be"
        "registered, but the opportunities for further processing are limited.\n"
        "If you believe that personal data about you is incorrect or incomplete, or you have filed"
        "a complaint against the processing of your data (read more about this below), you have the"
        "right to demand to demand that the processing of your personal data be limited temporarily."
        "This means that processing will be limited until, if relevant, we have rectified your "
        "personal data, or until we have been able to assess whether your complaint is justified."
        "In other circumstances you may also demand a more permanent limitation on the processing"
        "of your personal data. In order to qualify for the right to limit processing of personal "
        "data, the conditions established by the Personal Data Act and Article 18 of the GDPR must"
        "be met. If we receive a request from you to limit processing of your personal data, we "
        "will assess whether the statutory conditions have been met.\n\n"

        "Right to erasure\n"
        "In certain circumstances you have the right to demand that we erase your personal data. "
        "The right to erasure is not unconditional, and whether this applies to your situation must"
        "be assessed in light of relevant privacy legislation, i.e. the Personal Data Act and GDPR."
        "Please contact us if you want to have your personal data erased. It is important that you"
        "justify why you want the personal data erased, and, if possible, that you also specify "
        "which personal data you want erased. We will then consider whether the conditions for "
        "erasure, as established by law, have been met. Please be advised that the law allows for us"
        "to make exceptions to your right to erasure. For example, we may need to store personal "
        "data for the purpose of performing a task in compliance of the Act Relating to Universities"
        "and University Colleges, or for reasons of public interest, such as archiving, research and"
        "statistics.\n\n"

        "Right to object\n"
        "You may have the right to file an objection against the processing, i.e. object to the "
        "processing, on grounds that you have a specific need to stop the processing, e.g. if you "
        "have a need for protection, have a secret address, etc. The right to object is not "
        "unconditional, and it is contingent upon the legal basis for the processing, and on your "
        "particular circumstances. The conditions are established by Article 21 of the GDPR. If you"
        "object to processing of your personal data, we will consider whether the conditions for "
        "filing an objection have been met. If we find that you have the right to object to the "
        "processing and that your objection is justified, we will discontinue processing, and you "
        "will have the right to demand erasure of the data. Please be advised that we, under certain"
        "circumstances, may make exceptions from erasure, e.g. if we have to store your personal "
        "data for the purpose of performing a task in compliance with the Act Relating to "
        "Universities and University Colleges, or for reasons of public interest.\n\n"

        "Right to file complaint against processing\n"
        "If you believe we processed your personal data incorrectly or unlawfully, or if you believe"
        "we failed to protect your rights, you have the right to file a complaint against processing."
        "Please see item 10 below for how to contact us.\n"
        "If we dismiss your complaint, you may file your complaint with the Norwegian Data "
        "Protection Authority (DPA). The DPA is responsible for making sure Norwegian enterprises "
        "comply with the provisions of the Personal Data Act and the GDPR in their processing of "
        "personal data.\n\n"

        "10) Contact information\n"
        "Data Controller\n\n"
        "Your University/University College is the data controller of personal data in the Student"
        "ID app, cf. GDPR Article 4 no. 7.\n"

        "If you wish to exercise your rights as established in item 9 above, please contact your "
        "University/University College.\n\n"
    </string>

    <string name="delete_profile_title">Are you sure ?</string>
    <string name="delete_profile_desc">Your profile will be permanently deleted from system. You need to register again to login again. Do you want to continue</string>
    <string name="profile_deleted">Your profile is deleted from system.</string>
    <string name="something_went_wrong">Something went wrong, please try again later.</string>

</resources>
